你觉得如何
So, what do you think?
新发型  项链  裙子
New haircut? Necklace? Dress?
靴子  靴子
Boots? Boots!
比我平常买的靴子贵一点  也比租的贵
Now, they're a little more than I usually spend on boots. Or rent.
我的天啊
Oh, my God.
我知道
I know.
我会怀念温饱的日子
I'll miss being able to afford food.
对不起  它们真的很漂亮
I'm sorry. They just looked so good.
专柜小姐的表情像是在说
The saleswoman was looking at me like:
"这些靴子大贵了  你买不起"
"These are too expensive for you."
很有道理
She had a point.
莫妮卡  这双靴子好漂亮哦
Oh, Monica, those boots are amazing.
这是我的
They're mine!
很遗憾我们得退回去
Too bad we're gonna have to return them.
退回去  靴子听得见你说话
Return them? They're gonna hear you.
亲爱的  我不会去退货的
Honey, I'm not returning them.
我知道价格很贵  但我会经常穿
I know they cost a lot, but I'll wear them all the time.
你会看到的  而且我喜欢听到赞美
You'll see. Besides, I love the compliments.
你曾经拥有过美到大家都想拥有的东西吗
Have you ever had something so beautiful, everyone wants it?
我拥有你
I have you.
说得好  这靴子我留定了
Nice try. I'm keeping the boots.
《老友记》  第八季 第10集  莫妮卡的皮靴
Friends S08E10 The One With Monica's Boots
没错  我爱你
That's right. I love you.
我会一直跟你玩
And I'm gonna play with you all the time.
你怎么能让他对着你的胯下说话
How can you let him talk to your crotch like that?
他是在跟宝宝说话  原来如此
He's talking to the baby.  Oh! Okay.
好吧  因为当他说
Okay, because when he said,
"我等不及要听到你说第一句话"
"I can't wait for your first words"...
我想"这招不错"
...I thought, "There's a trick."
我得走了  待会见
Well, I gotta go, you guys. I'll see you later.
好吧  拜拜  拜
Okay. Bye.  Bye.
瑞秋  你能帮我一个忙吗
Hey, Rach, listen. Can you do me a favor?
我之前见过我妹妹
I was talkin' to my sister
她知道你在拉夫罗兰工作..
and she knows you you work at Ralph Lauren...
算了  绝对不行
Forget it. No way.
我不会再把拉夫罗兰的衣服寄到监狱
I am not sending more Ralph Lauren clothes to prison.
那是在暴珍天物  不  不是她
It is a waste.  No, not her.
我最小的妹妹蒂娜对流行服装很有兴趣
My youngest sister, Dina, she is interested in fashion.
她想跟成功人士谈谈  给她一些建议
She wants to talk to someone successful to give her some advice.
我想我可以跟我的上司谈一谈
I guess I could talk to my supervisors.
不  她想跟你谈
No, she wants to talk to you.
真的吗  天啊  我是成功人士
Really? Oh, my God. I'm successful.
你能跟她见个面吗
Okay, so would you meet with her?
我很乐意  请她来找我吧
Yes, I'd love to. Have her come by the office.
谢谢  你会喜欢她的
Great, thanks. You'll love her so much.
她是崔比安尼家最聪明的孩子
She's the smartest of all the Tribbiani children.
你知道学术评量测验吗  知道
Yeah, you know the SATs?  Yeah.
她有考过
She took them.
罗斯  本念的是史密斯菲德小学吧
Ross, doesn't Ben go to Smithfield Day School?
对  怎么了
Yeah. Why?
史汀的儿子也在那里念书
Sting has a son that goes there too.
我知道  他跟本是同班同学
I know. He's in Ben's class.
你知道却一直没有告诉我们
You knew and never said anything?
只知道跟我们说那些笨恐龙的事情
With all the stupid dinosaur stuff you tell us?
好吧  我不会再说恐龙的事了
Fine, no more dinosaur stuff.
我能谈谈化石吗
Can I talk about fossils?
"史汀七岁大的儿子"  还有他的照片
"Sting's son, 7 years old." And there's a picture.
你在看什么
What are you reading,
"曼哈顿私立学校学童绑架指南"
"The Kidnapper's Guide to Manattan Private Schools"?
我在看《纽约杂志》
It's New York Magazine.
报导城里最棒的学校
It's an article about best schools in the city.
你跟史汀很熟吗
So how well do you know Sting?
事实上我没有见过他
I actually haven't even met him.
那真的很糟糕
Yeah. That's too bad.
我真的很想去听他星期五的演唱会
I really wanna go to his concert Friday night,
但票卖完了
but it's totally sold out.
我知道了  你为什么不去跟他要票
I know! Why don't you meet him and get tickets.
如果你可以要到两张  我就带你去
If you get two, I'll take you.
明天我会去接本  或许他会在那里
Actually, I'm picking Ben up tomorrow. Maybe he'll be there.
这就对了  你真是幸运
There you go. You're so lucky.
明天你可能就会看到史汀了
You might get to meet Sting tomorrow.
生小孩就是好处多啊
That's why you have kids.
嗨  大伙们
Hey, guys.
嗨  莫妮卡  嗨  靴子
Hi, Monica. Hi, boots.
看吧  钱德勒
See, Chandler?
我已经开始经常穿了
I'm getting a lot of use out of them already.
真的很实用
They're very practical.
可以搭配连衣裙  短裙  长裤
You can wear them with dresses, with skirts, with pants...
你可以搭配短裤  站在街角
You wear them with shorts on the corner
赚点钱来付靴子的帐单
and earn the money to pay for them.
哇  好漂亮
Wow, they're beautiful.
真的很磨脚
They hurt so much.
什么  做这双靴子的人
What?  The guy who made these...
一定很讨厌脚  想要看着它们死掉
...hates feet and wants to see them die.
把它们送给我
Give them to me.
我的脚好几年没有感觉了
I haven't felt my feet in years.
不行  我花了大价钱买下来
I can't. I spent so much money on them
我告诉钱德勒我会一直穿着
and I told Chandler I'd wear them all the time.
我不能送人
I can't just give them away.
你可以拿去退货换钱
Then get your money back and return them.
我也不能那么做
I can't do that either.
鞋底的地方有磨损
The soles are already a little scuffed up,
内衬沾满了我的血
and the insides are filled with my blood.
我刚刚去学校接了本
Hey, I just picked up Ben from school.
你的任务还没完成吧
I don't think you did a very thorough job.
我把他送回卡罗尔家了
I dropped him off at Carol's.
总之  我没有要到门票
Anyway, it turns out I'm not gonna get those tickets, though.
不是吧  为什么
Oh, no. Why not?
结果本跟史汀的儿子处得不好
It turns out Ben and Sting's son do not get along.
怎么会呢
How come?
很明显  史汀的儿子取笑
Apparently, Sting's son made fun of the fact that
本的妈妈们是女同志
Ben's moms are "lesbenims."
等一下  如果他们处不好
Wait, Ross. If they don't get along,
那你应该帮他们劝和
then you should smooth things over.
让他们做好朋友
Make them be friends.
你不能逼孩子们做朋友  当然可以
Phoebe, you can't force kids to be friends.  Sure you can.
给他们一些积木  让他们在游戏床里玩
Give them some blocks. Put them in a playpen.
游戏床  本都七岁了  七岁了
Playpen? Ben's 7.  Your kid is 7?
他个头好小哦
He's really small.
拜托你去要门票
Please get the tickets.
抱歉  菲比  我办不到
I'm sorry, Pheebs. I just can't do it.
不  你可以  史汀亲口说过
Yes, you can. Sting says so himself.
什么  罗斯可以
What?  Ross can.
听着  我很抱歉
Look, I'm sorry...
罗斯可以
Ross can.
菲比  罗斯可以帮我要到门票
Phoebe?  Ross can get me the tickets.
罗斯可以帮我要到门票
Ross can get me the tickets.
她来了  未来的流行界超级巨星
Here she is: Future fashion superstar.
乔伊  我还算不上...  我妹妹蒂娜
Oh, Joey, I'm hardly...  My little sister Dina.
蒂娜  很高兴见到你  嗨
Hi, Dina. Nice to meet you.  Hi.
谢谢你答应见我
Thanks so much for meeting with me.
乔伊告诉我很多关于你的事
Joey's told me so much about you.
她好兴奋哦
This is so exciting for her.
我让你们两个"流行大师"
Well, I'll let you two "fashists"
坐下来好好谈正事
get down to business.
好吧  蒂娜
Okay. All right, Dina.
我们来谈谈  你可以考虑的
Well, let's talk about the different areas of fashion...
服装界的不同领域
...that you could get involved in.
让我看看  有设计部门
Let's see, there's design.
但那得需要相关文凭
But you may need a whole other degree for that.
销售部门不错  你可以旅行
There's sales which is great, because you get to travel.
我不在乎流行服装
I don't care about fashion.
我怀孕了  我知道你也是  你得帮帮我
I'm pregnant. And I know you are too, so you gotta help me.
还有行销部门
Then there's marketing.
怎么了  没事  我只是在打哈欠
What's wrong?  Nothing. I just was yawning.
别忘了今晚我公司要办派对
Don't forget, my office holiday party's tonight.
我们今晚不一定要去  对吧
Honey, we don't really have to go to this thing, do we?
我知道你不喜欢参加我公司的派对
Sweetie, I know that you don't like my office parties,
但你可以穿你的新靴子
but you can wear your new boots.
看吧  每件事都有它好的一面
See? Every cloud has a supple leather lining.
今晚我不想穿靴子  为什么
I don't wanna wear the boots tonight.  Why not?
我担心你老板看到以后
Well, you know. I'm worried your bosses will see them
会觉得他们给你的薪水太高了
and think they pay you too much money.
或是你的助理看到以后会要求加薪
Or your assistant will see them and want a raise.
你以为我是在帮靴子订价的公司上班吗
Do you think I work some kind of bootpricing company?
我已经挑好了我要穿的衣服
I picked out this outfit I wanna wear,
靴子跟它不配
and the boots don't go with it.
你说过这双靴子物有所值
You said that you paid all that money
因为可以搭配短裙  连衣裙跟长裤
because those boots go with skirts, dresses, and pants!
好吧  你要我穿靴子我就穿嘛
Fine. If you want me to, I'll wear the boots.
事实上我要到卧室去试穿我的衣服
In fact, I'll go into my room right now and try the outfit on.
穿着我的靴子参加圣诞节派对
Christmas party in my boots!
我不能进去  我不敢告诉他
I can't go in there. I can't tell him.
一定会没事的
It's gonna be okay.
他一直都非常支持我
He has been incredibly supportive of me.
如果他大发脾气
And if he gets a little upset,
快把肉饼赛百味三明治拿给他
that's what the meatball sub is for.
谢谢  好吧
Thank you.  Okay.
我的流行界女王们回来了
Hey! It's my fashion girls.
怎么了  你为什么不坐下呢
What's wrong?  Why don't you sit down.
蒂娜有件事想告诉你
Dina has something that she wants to tell you.
发生了什么事  是妈妈吗  她生病了吗
What's going on? Is it Mom? Is she sick?
是爸爸的心脏出问题了吗
Is it Dad's heart?
那是三明治吗
Is that a sandwich?
妈妈跟爸爸没事  那是三明治吗
Joe, Mom and Dad are fine.  Is that a sandwich?!
乔伊  有件事你得知道
Joey, there's something that you should know.
蒂娜
Dina?
我怀孕了  什么
I'm pregnant.   What?
快给他三明治  给他三明治
Now. Give him the sandwich! Give him the sandwich!
很明显  这是个误会  你不可能怀孕
Obviously, this is a mistake. You can't be pregnant.
因为你得先做爱才会怀孕
Because you have to have sex to get pregnant.
乔伊  我试着学你一样等到25岁再尝禁果
Joe, I tried to wait until I was 25, like you did.
什么  蒂娜...
What? Dina...
我不敢相信  你是个好孩子
I can't believe this. You're the good one.
你念过大学  还念了两年
You went to college! Both years!
是谁干的
Who did this to you?
巴比·科索  但他是个很好的人
Bobby Corso. But he's a real nice guy.
我很喜欢他  他很好笑
I like him a lot. He's real funny.
你因为"好笑"而怀孕
You got pregnant for "funny"?
蒂娜  如果他很好笑  你只要笑就行了
Dina, if he's funny, laugh!
我马上回来  你留在这里
I'll be back in a little while. You stay here!
为什么  你要去哪里
Why? Where you going?
我现在没法直视你
I can't look at you right now.
我知道
I know.
你在这里啊  本
Oh, there you are, Ben.
菲比阿姨  你来这里做什么
Aunt Phoebe, what are you doing here?
我听说你跟班里的一个男生
Well, I heard you're having a problem
相处得不太好
with one of the boys in your class.
所以我就想过来  让你们坐下来
So I thought I'd come down here and sit you both down,
好好地谈一谈  把问题解决掉
have a little talk and make it all okay.
那个孩子叫做史汀的儿子
Now, the boy's name is Sting's son.
杰克  我恨他  他是个混蛋
Jack? I hate him. He's a jerk.
本  有时候人们外表看起来像是混蛋
Now, Ben. Sometimes people may seem like jerks on the outside...
但他们有个名人爸爸
...but they have famous fathers.
我得走了  我朋友道格在等我
I have to go. My friend Doug is waiting for me over there.
你就跟这种孩子做朋友
Him, you're friends with.
对不起  需要我帮忙吗
Excuse me, can I help you with something?
对  我在找杰克的父母
Yes. I'm looking for Jack's parents.
你是家长吗  我来找本
Are you with one of the students?  I'm with Ben.
你是本的妈妈
Are you one of Ben's mothers?
我是本的妈妈
I am one of Ben's mothers.
我是女同志
I'm a lesbian.
我爸妈很难接受这种事
It was difficult coming out to my parents.
我是珍妮·布恩  新来的老师
Well, hi. I'm Jenny Boon. I'm a new teacher here.
我只见过你的另一半卡罗尔
I've only met your partner, Carol.
那么我就是苏珊
That would make me Susan.
对  你要找杰克父母
Right. Are you looking for Jack's parents
讨论他跟本的问题吗
to discuss his problems he's having with Ben?
是啊  我觉得父母们
Yeah, because I really do think the parents
应该坐下来好好谈一谈
should sit down together and have a conversation.
对  我们就那么办吧
Yeah, let's do that!
听起来很不错
That sounds good.
我们应该坐下来谈一谈
We should sit down and talk.
我和爱人卡罗尔跟史汀夫妇
Just me, my lover, Carol, and the Stings.
我要怎么联络他们
How will I get in touch with them?
联络簿上有他们的电话号码
Their number's on the contact sheet.
能给我一份吗
Could I get a copy of that?
卡罗尔把它丢了  她弄丢了我们的联络簿
Carol threw it out. She lost ours.
她真的很糊涂
She's such a scatterbrain.
但天啊  她的屁股真是火辣性感
But, man, what a hot piece of ass.
那场派对还不错
You know, that party wasn't bad.
对  我不知道还有舞会
Yeah. I didn't know there'd be dancing.
那真是个大惊喜
That was a fun surprise.
我看不到计程车  或许我们该走回家
I don't see a cab. Maybe we should walk.
不  我们不能走路
No, we can't walk.
离地铁站只有15条街远  来吧
It's 15 blocks to the subway. Come on.
你觉得我们可以从那个下水道孔
Do you think we can get to the subway right there
直接爬到地铁站里吗
if we climb through that manole cover?
什么事不对劲吗
What's going on?
我走不动了  好吗
I can't walk, okay?
买这双靴子是个天大的错误  什么
These boots were a huge mistake.  What?
你说得对  我不该买下来
Okay, you were right. I never should have bought them.
害我的脚好痛  我的脚趾快断了
They're killing me, one toe at a time.
我说得对  原来"对了"就是这种感觉
So I was right. This is what it feels like to be right.
我为什么觉得很不安
It's oddly unsettling.
我们要怎么回家  背着走吧
How are we gonna we get home? Maybe a piggyback ride?
来吧  好吧  等一下
Hop on.  Okay, wait, just give me a second.
我先把靴子脱掉
Let me just get my boots off first.
天啊
Oh, God.
亲爱的  我知道你很痛
Honey, I know you're in pain right now,
但我却来了性致
but I'm a little turnedon.
你会不会担心走路的时候
Do you ever worry that you'll be walking
宝宝会掉出来
and your baby will just slip out?
你念的哪所大学  蒂娜
What college was that, Dina?
天啊  巴比
Oh, my God. Bobby?
蒂娜  很高兴能见到你
Hi, Dina. Good to see you.
乔伊  你在做什么
Joey, what are you doing?
我只是在做我该做的事
Just what needs to be done.
亲爱的亲友们  我们齐聚一堂
Dearly beloved, we're gathered here...
乔伊  这太疯狂了
Joey, this is crazy.
我在跟上帝说话  别打断我
Don't interrupt me when I'm talking to God!
我们说到哪里了
Where were we?
你  蒂娜  愿意嫁这个人...  不
Right, okay. Do you Dina take this man...?  No!
你得嫁他  不  我不会嫁
You'll take him.  No, I won't!
这可由不得你  不  我就愿意这样
You don't get a say in this.  Yes, I do.
我听到了"我愿意"  已经完成一半
I heard "I do." We're halfway there.
再来是你
Okay. You.
好吧  乔伊  够了
All right, Joey, that is enough!
虽然这个婚礼既漂亮又温馨
Listen. As beautiful and moving as this ceremony is,
这是不合法的
this is not legal.
他们没有结婚证书
Okay. They don't have a marriage license
也没有证婚人
and they don't have any witnesses,
而且新郎只穿了一只鞋
and the groom only has one shoe.
对  他把另一只鞋脱了  用来打我
Yeah, he took the other one off and hit me with it.
我该怎么办
What am I supposed to do?
你应该了解他们是成年人
You're supposed to realize they are adults
可以自己做决定
and that can make their own decisions.
不  他们不能  他们笨到让自己怀孕
No, they can't. They were stupid enough to get knocked up!
预防措施不一定有效对吧
Contraceptives are not always effective. Right?
对  我们没有做预防措施
Yeah. We kind of didn't use any.
孩子们  别帮倒忙了
Come on, kids, a little help here!
这个地方真的很棒
Wow! This place is incredible!
史汀的笔...
Sting's pen...
他送给了菲比
...that he gave to Phoebe.
来吧  秘密通道
Come on, secret passageway.
我是楚蒂  你一定是本的妈妈
I'm Trudie. You must be Ben's mum.
不然我为什么要到这里来呢
Why else would I be here?
请坐
Why don't you sit down.
我知道杰克跟本最近处得不太好
I gather Jack and Ben haven't been getting along lately.
我相信这个故事一定有两面说法
I'm sure there are two sides to this story.
但我听到的是本是个"大笨蛋"
But all I've heard is that Ben's a bit of a "poopoohead."
抱歉  杰克的爸爸不会来吗
I'm sorry, won't Jack's father be joining us?
对不起  杰克的爸爸没空
Well, I'm sorry. Jack's father's not available.
好吧  我们可以改约到周五晚上
Okay. Well, then, could we reschedule for Friday night,
八点见行吗
perhaps at 8:00?
不  那样行不通
No, I know that wouldn't work.
我丈夫要办演唱会
My husband's in concert.
演唱会
Concert. Yeah.
这让问题变得有点棘手
That does put us in quite a pickle.
演唱会前后我都有事
Because you see I'm busy before and after the concert,
演唱会的时间他又很忙
and he's obviously busy during.
我想你跟我现在该来谈谈杰克跟本的事
So I guess you and I should talk about Jack and Ben right now.
除非...
Unless... Unless...
我愿意到演唱会上...
Okay, I would be willing to go to the concert...
想一想孩子们的事
...all the while thinking about the children, of course.
你是来要票的吗
Are you here for tickets?
谢谢  四张就够了
Thank you. Four would be great.
我不会把演唱会门票
I'm not giving concert tickets
送给这样利用自己孩子的人
to someone who'd use their son like this.
那正好  本不是我的儿子
Then you're in luck. Ben's not my son.
听着  我已经按下了静声警铃
Look, I've just pressed a button triggering a silent alarm.
警察随时会到
Any minute now, the police will be here.
"警察乐队"要来？
The Police? Here?
他们要复合了
A reunion?
好吧  已经走了十条街  只剩五条
Okay, 10 blocks down. Five to go.
等一下  停
Oh, wait! Stop, stop!
抱歉  你需要休息吗
Oh, I'm sorry. Do you need a break?
是棕黄色的同款靴子
My boots in tan!
你能靠近一点  让我看看价钱吗
Can you get a little closer so I see the price?
我在这里就看到了 它会害你丢掉一个老公
I can see it from right here. It'll cost you one husband.
抱歉  我可以自己走了
I'm sorry. I can walk the rest of the way now.
把我的靴子还给我
Just give me my boots.
我没有拿你的靴子
I don't have your boots.
我也没拿  那在哪里
I don't have them either. Where are they?
你为什么不去看看鞍囊里有没有
Why don't you check in one of my saddlebags
我先去吃点草
while I chew on a bale of hay?
好吧  天啊  我们得回去找靴子
Okay. My God, we gotta go back and get them!
亲爱的  你还会再穿那双靴子吗
Hoeny, are you ever gonna wear the boots again?
好吧  我再也不会穿了
Okay, I'll never wear them again.
我只是还没机会说再见
I just didn't get a chance to say goodbye.
你可以跟棕黄色的靴子说再见
You know what? You can say goodbye to the tan ones.
好吧  好吧
Okay. All right.  Okay.
再见  靴子  等一下  打五折
Bye, boots. Wait! Half off!
乔伊  他们不打算结婚
Joey, just because they're not getting married
不代表这就是件坏事
doesn't mean this is gonna be a disaster.
或许他们有计划
Maybe they have a plan.
好吧  我们听听他们的计划
Oh, okay, let's hear their plan.
蒂娜跟巴比会有什么样的未来
Now, what's the future look like for Dina and Bobby?
这个嘛...
Well...
我对我的乐队期望很高
...I really have high hopes for my band.
你说得对  他是很好笑  等一下
You were right. He is funny.  Now, wait a minute.
我敢说你一开始告诉大家
I bet when you told people
你要当演员  大家都笑你
you wanted to be an actor, they laughed at you.
来吧  巴比  跟我们谈谈你的乐队
Come on, Bobby, tell us a little bit about your band.
团员只有我跟我朋友鲁斯特
Well, it's just me and my pal Rooster.
乐队名字叫做"呆瓜"
The band's name is Numbnuts.
真的吗
Really?
蒂娜  如果你要生孩子  你应该结婚
Dina, if you're having a baby, you should be married.
即使是嫁给巴比  我不是在夸奖你
Even if it is to Bobby. Dude, that's not a compliment.
乔伊  我就知道你不会支持我
Joey, I knew you wouldn't be supportive.
你打算怎么办
So, what are you gonna do?
你要生下孩子  自己带大吗
You're gonna have the baby and raise it by yourself?
没有丈夫帮你
Without a husband?
你没办法当单亲妈妈
You can't be a single mother alone!
你会毁了自己的一生
You're gonna ruin your life!
对不起  我在自毁人生吗
Excuse me. Am I ruining my life?
不  你不一样
No, it's different for you.
你很坚强独立
You're so strong and together.
你不是不知道自己在做什么的笨小孩
You're not some dumb kid who doesn't know what she's doing.
你说什么
Excuse me?
我一次只能跟一个孕妇说话
One pregnant woman at a time, please!
我只是希望你过得好
I just want you to be okay.
逼她嫁给巴比  她就会过得好吗
So forcing her to marry Bobby is gonna make that happen?
或许吧
Maybe.
对  "呆瓜"主要做什么类型的音乐
Yeah. So, what kind of music does Numbnuts...?
算了  我办不到
Oh, forget it! I can't!
乔伊  这件事真的让我很害怕
Joey, I am scared to death about this.
但我想我办得到  我只是需要帮助
But I really think I can do it. I'm just gonna need some help.
巴比会一直陪着我  没错
Bobby's gonna be here the whole time.  You bet I am.
至于你刚刚问的那个问题
And to answer your earlier question,
我们唱纯粹的匪帮说唱
we're straightup gangster rap.
瑞秋告诉我你一直都很支持她
Look, Rachel's told me how much easier you've made all this on her.
你为什么不能支持我
Why can't you do that for me?
因为你是我的妹妹
Because you're my baby sister!
你是我哥哥
And you're my big brother.
你是我全世界最喜欢的人
I mean, you're my favorite guy in the whole world.
我甚至不怕告诉妈妈跟爸爸
I'm not even scared to tell Mom and Dad.
我害怕告诉你
I was scared of telling you.
我也会怕他们  但好吧
I'd be scared of them, but all right.
想到你会因为我怀孕而生我的气
Joey, I can't stand the thought of having this baby
我就受不了
with you mad at me.
我要他有舅舅
I want him to have his uncle.
我的宝宝会有乔伊舅舅吗
Is my baby gonna have his Uncle Joey?
他当然会有乔伊舅舅
Of course he's gonna have his Uncle Joey.
我们会没事的
We'll be all right.
即使我们没结婚  宝宝还是会得到宠爱
I mean, even if we're not married, this baby is gonna be so loved.
不只是我们会爱他  没错
And not just by us.  That's right.
他的舅舅也会爱他
By his uncle too.
还有你
And by you.
巴比  我们还是过来
Okay, Bobby, why don't we come over here
让他们独处一下吧
and let them have a little moment, okay?
过来
Come here.
不  说真的  你到底有什么问题
No, seriously, what's wrong with you?
你一定爱死我了
You're gonna love me so much.
我弄到史汀的门票了
I got Sting tickets!
天啊  我真的爱你  你怎么办到的
Oh, my God, I do love you! How did you do it?
就说
Well, let's just say:
罗斯真厉害
Rose can!
座位是哪一区  在中间包厢
Where are the seats?  Middle balcony.
我们的位置离史汀  他太太
Okay. Would you say that's more than 50 yards away
还有他的家人超过50码吗
from Sting, his wife or a member of his family?
对  那样就不犯法  我可以去
Yeah.  Then that's not breaking the law. I'm there!